sinnersattire.com 2019-11-30

# Privacy - SINNERS ATTIRE

**1\. General Information**

This privacy notice sets out the ways in which SINNERS ATTIRE LTD, company number 09052680, collects, processes and shares your personal data.

**2.  ** **What information do  we collect?**

SINNERS ATTIRE may collect, process and use the following information you provide during the purchase of goods online, when you purchase a gift voucher & when your sign up to our newsletter online

  * address;
  * email address;
  * telephone number;

**3\. What is your data used for?**

SINNERS ATTIRE processes your personal data in the following ways, and on the following legal bases:

  * Your name, telephone and email address for the purposes of sending you direct electronic marketing. SINNERS ATTIRE will only do this if you have given your consent to being provided with the direct electronic marketing. You may opt-out of receiving this at any time by contacting sales@sinnersattire.com or by changing your preferences.
  * To carry out SINNERS ATTIRE's obligations arising from any contracts entered into between SINNERS ATTIRE and you, for example to take payment or gift voucher.
  * To send you a confirmation email or text message to verify and confirm your order and gift voucher orders, this is necessary for the performance of SINNERS ATTIRE's contract with you so that it can confirm your order and provide you with details about your voucher. It is also in SINNERS ATTIRE's legitimate interests to ensure that customers are reminded about their orders.
  * To enhance your experience of the SINNERS ATTIRE website, we do this as it is in our legitimate interest to ensure that you receive the best experience possible online and shopping with us.
  * To optimise your experience of the types of direct electronic marketing that SINNERS ATTIRE sends you (where you have consented to direct electronic marketing). SINNERS ATTIRE does this on the basis that it is necessary in our legitimate interest to ensure that such direct marketing is of interest and use to you.
  * Any other purposes where we have obtained your consent to do so.

We may use your information in an anonymised and/or aggregated manner in order to analyse the data so that we can enhance our IT systems or website and carry out research. We may share this anonymised and/or aggregated data with third parties, but you will not be identifiable from any such data.

SINNERS ATTIRE may review your personal data if it has reason to believe that the information has been provided inappropriately, unlawfully or illegally. SINNERS ATTIRE does this on the basis that it is necessary in its legitimate interest to ensure that the restaurants and website are being used appropriately, lawfully and legally.

**4\. Disclosing Information**

SINNERS ATTIRE does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personal identifiable information to outside parties other than as set out in this privacy notice.

SINNERS ATTIRE provides your personal data:

  * to selected third party providers in order to process and deliver your bookings and orders, for example payment providers, gift voucher merchants and third party online booking providers;
  * to selected marketing agencies, web-mailing companies and hosting companies;
  * to other companies in the same group of companies as SINNERS ATTIRE. These companies will only use your personal data in the same way as SINNERS ATTIRE can under this privacy policy; and
  * credit reference agencies or fraud prevention agencies.

SINNERS ATTIRE will only transfer your personal data outside of the EEA to organisations who have adequate safeguards in place to ensure the security of your personal data.

SINNERS ATTIRE will disclose your personal data to third parties:

  * if SINNERS ATTIRE sells or buys any business or assets, in which case SINNERS ATTIRE will disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or asset;
  * if SINNER ATTIRE or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets; or
  * if SINNER ATTIRE is under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of SINNERS ATTIRE, you or any third party, and to investigate illegal activities and breaches of any agreement SINNERS ATTIRE has with you. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

SINNERS ATTIRE may pass your personal data to third parties in a statistical and/or aggregated manner in order to analyse the data. SINNERS ATTIRE will always ensure that you are not identifiable from any such data.

We may otherwise share your information as directed by you or subject to your consent.

**5\. Protecting your personal data**

SINNERS ATTIRE has put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, it limits access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know and in accordance with this privacy notice. They will only process your personal data in accordance with SINNERS ATTIRE's instructions.

SINNERS ATTIRE has put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where it is legally required to do so.

You play an important role in keeping your information secure. If you have any reason to believe that your interactions with us are no longer secure, then please contact us at sales@sinnersattire.com

**6\. Holding your personal data**

SINNERS ATTIRE will retain your data for as long as we need to hold it in order to provide you with services and to improve, analyse and optimise your customer experience.

We may also retain your data for further periods where we need to do so in order comply with any legal or regulatory requirements (including keeping certain records for seven years for VAT purposes), to carry out audits, to detect and prevent fraud, to enforce contracts or to resolve any disputes.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, SINNERS ATTIRE considers the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which SINNERS ATTIRE processes your personal data and whether those purposes can be achieved through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

**7\. Your Rights**

Where SINNERS ATTIRE relies on consent as the condition for processing your personal data, for example for sending you electronic direct marketing, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time.

You have various statutory rights in relation to your personal data. In particular, you have the right to:

  * object to direct marketing communications at any time;
  * request and obtain access to your personal data;
  * rectification or erasure of your personal data, in certain circumstances;
  * object to or restrict the processing of your personal data in certain circumstances;
  * have your personal data stored in a manner in which it is portable from the environment in which it is stored by SINNERS ATTIRE to another environment; and
  * file a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office.

**8\. Changes to Privacy Notice**

If SINNERS ATTIRE decides to change this privacy notice, any changes will be posted on this page.

This privacy notice was last modified on 5th May 2018

**9\. Contact**

If you wish to contact SINNERS ATTIRE in relation to this privacy notice, including in relation to any of the rights set out in section 7 above, please contact us at sales@sinnersattire.com

 **Text Marketing and notifications: By subscribing to text notifications you agree to receive recurring automated marketing messages at the phone number provided. Consent is not a condition of purchase. Reply STOP to unsubscribe. HELP for help. Msg & Data rates may apply. More info view Privacy Policy and ToS.**
